{
    "subject": "resource/Sebastian_Junger",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/name",
    "object": "Sebastian Junger",
    "human_readable": "Sebastian Junger's name is Sebastian Junger.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9782984852790833,
            "question": "What is Sebastian Junger's full name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9367886781692505,
            "question": "Is Sebastian Junger a known author?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8903692960739136,
            "question": "What type of work is Sebastian Junger known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8671206831932068,
            "question": "Where is Sebastian Junger from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.787427544593811,
            "question": "Has Sebastian Junger collaborated with other authors or filmmakers?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.621068000793457,
            "question": "Has Sebastian Junger won any awards for his writing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6140939593315125,
            "question": "Are there any popular books written by Sebastian Junger?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6109304428100586,
            "question": "Does Sebastian Junger have any other notable achievements besides writing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5910211801528931,
            "question": "What are some common themes explored in Sebastian Junger's work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5731054544448853,
            "question": "What inspired Sebastian Junger to become a writer?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Sebastian Junger's name is Sebastian Junger.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7741_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some common themes explored in Sebastian Junger's work?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7741_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Sebastian Junger have any other notable achievements besides writing?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7741_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any popular books written by Sebastian Junger?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7741_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7741_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7741_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7741_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7741_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7741_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7741_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7741_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7741_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7741_94.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7741_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents clearly mention that Sebastian Junger is an American journalist, author, and filmmaker. Therefore, the statement \"Sebastian Junger's name is Sebastian Junger\" is correct based on the provided context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}